So at first as you see it asks us to describe an image or drop reference images with a prompt to edit
So this is the first thing that we have image generator
But as you see it says itself. It mentions itself that it is not
Just a generator, but it also can edit but first let's say that for example. I want to generate an image
out of aliens walking
Near the Eiffel Tower, right so for example, I need that image for some purpose
So what I do is that I come here and typed type my prompt, you know, I want an image of
aliens
Walking in Paris for example with the I fill
tower
in the
background, right and
The more accurate and the better and the more detailed that we want our images to be we can just add details to this very prompt that we're writing, right?